[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the nationality of Erno Rubik, the inventor of the 3-D mechanical puzzle, known as the Rubiks Cube?", "correct_answer": "Hungarian", "incorrect_answers": ["American", "Polish", "French"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular Grammy Award-winning female singer and songwriter made her acting debut in the 1999 drama movie Music of the Heart, starring Meryl Streep?", "correct_answer": "Gloria Estefan", "incorrect_answers": ["Nelly Furtado", "Mary J. Blige", "Rihanna"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This non-government anti-AIDS organization was founded by Bono and Bobby Shriver in 2002 with start up capital from Bill Gates.", "correct_answer": "Debt, AIDS, Trade in Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Live Aid", "Band Aid", "USA for Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of character does Jennifer Aniston play in the 2009 romantic drama movie Love Happens?", "correct_answer": "Florist", "incorrect_answers": ["Pastry chef", "Writer", "Waitress"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The smallpox isnt dangerous.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This war movie was the first movie to win the  Academy Award for Best Picture.", "correct_answer": "Wings", "incorrect_answers": ["Ben-Hur", "Gone With The Wind", "Patton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the seventh rule of Fight Club?", "correct_answer": "Fights go on as long as they have to.", "incorrect_answers": ["You dont talk about Fight Club.", "No shirts, no shoes.", "When someone says stop or goes limp, the fight is over."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Venus is the third brightest object in the sky after the Sun and what other object?", "correct_answer": "The Moon", "incorrect_answers": ["Proxima Centuri", "Aldeberan", "Sirius"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the first cartoon cat that was created for the screen.", "correct_answer": "Felix", "incorrect_answers": ["Puddy Tat", "Rumple Teaser", "Katsenjammer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the Sanskrit word for \u201cunion?\u201d", "correct_answer": "yoga", "incorrect_answers": ["shiva", "sri", "krishna"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What singer and actress portrayed Gregs mother in the 2004 comedy movie Meet the Fockers?", "correct_answer": "Barbra Streisand", "incorrect_answers": ["Vanessa Williams", "Cher", "Tina Turner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This prion disease is also known as laughing sickness due to the outbursts of laughter that mark its second phase.", "correct_answer": "Kuru", "incorrect_answers": ["Creutzfeldt-Jakob Disease", "Scrapie", "None of these"]}]